[
 {
   "id": 1,
   "question": "4, 8, 16, ?",
   "answer": "32",
   "solution": "4, 8, 16, 32"
 },
 {
   "id": 2,
   "question": "2 + 2 x 2 = ?",
   "answer": "6",
   "solution": "2 + 2 x 2 = 6"
 },
 {
   "id": 3,
   "question": "A + A = 8\n2B + A = 14\nC + B = 11\nC = ?",
   "answer": "6",
   "solution": "A + A = 8\n2B + A = 14\nC + B = 11\nC = 6"
 },
 {
   "id": 4,
   "question": "6 = 30\n3 = 15\n7 = 35\n2 = ?",
   "answer": "10",
   "solution": "6 = 30\n3 = 15\n7 = 35\n2 = 10"
 },
 {
   "id": 5,
   "question": "4, 11, 18, ?",
   "answer": "25",
   "solution": "4, 11, 18, 25"
 },
 {
   "id": 6,
   "question": "5 + 5 x 5 - 5 = ?",
   "answer": "25",
   "solution": "5 + 5 x 5 - 5 = 25"
 },
 {
   "id": 7,
   "question": "A + B = 60\nA - B = 40\nA / B = ?",
   "answer": "5",
   "solution": "A = 50\nB = 10\nA / B = 5"
 },
 {
   "id": 8,
   "question": "A + B = 60\nA - B = 40\nA / B = ?",
   "answer": "5",
   "solution": "A = 50\nB = 10\nA / B = 5"
 },
 {
   "id": 9,
   "question": "13, 18 = 31\n7, 25 = 32\n12, 30 = 42\n26, 13 = ?",
   "answer": "39",
   "solution": "13, 18 = 31\n7, 25 = 32\n12, 30 = 42\n26, 13 = 39"
 },
 {
   "id": 10,
   "question": "8 - 8 / 4 x 3 = ?",
   "answer": "2",
   "solution": "8 - 8 / 4 x 3 = 2"
 }
]